<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title></title>
        <link>https://dangerousl.github.io</link>
        <description></description>
        <generator>Zola</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <atom:link href="https://dangerousl.github.io/tags/june-2020/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
            <item>
                <title>In Defense of Video Games: Maybe They Aren&#x27;t a Total Waste of Time</title>
                <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                <link>https://dangerousl.github.io/in-defense-of-video-games/</link>
                <guid>https://dangerousl.github.io/in-defense-of-video-games/</guid>
                <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;in-which-i-attempt-to-validate-my-most-significant-time-investment&quot;&gt;In Which I Attempt to Validate My Most Significant Time Investment&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was having a friendly discussion with a friend a few weeks ago, and during our chat something came up about using one&#x27;s time to be productive or to simply &amp;quot;consume.&amp;quot;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The breadth of different activities that could be considered productive or not was fairly vast, as is typical in this type of exchange, and generally we agreed. However, eventually it landed on video games.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I forget the exact words, and truthfully it doesn&#x27;t matter too much; I know that no harm was meant in the statement. Still, I ended up considering the thesis:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video games are a waste of time. The act of playing (or consuming) video game material does not &lt;em&gt;produce&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;, and therefore is not productive.&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I disagreed.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>You Should Listen: Thunder and Lightning - Thin Lizzy</title>
                <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                <link>https://dangerousl.github.io/ysl-thin-lizzy-thunder-lightning/</link>
                <guid>https://dangerousl.github.io/ysl-thin-lizzy-thunder-lightning/</guid>
                <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;this-is-the-one&quot;&gt;This Is The One&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Should Listen&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; is a thing where I post about some music that I&#x27;m (probably) listening to that I think would be great if we got together and listened to together. I&#x27;m not going to tell you where to find it or anything, but I might provide a track off youtube if I can find it. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, I make no promises to actually writing anything about these suggestions other than to just suggest them.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that out of the way...&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just imagine it now... I call you up on the telephone, hoping either you or one of your parents picks up and not your jerk older sibling that thinks we&#x27;re nerds. &amp;quot;Hey, want to come over and listen to some Thin Lizzy?&amp;quot;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe you&#x27;re tired of sitting around at home. Maybe you were just looking for an excuse to hang out and play some &lt;em&gt;Sword of Fargoal&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; on the C64.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, maybe you&#x27;re genuinely are interested to hear what I meant when you heard the garbled words &amp;quot;Thin Lizzy&#x27;s new LP&amp;quot; come through the corded phone hanging off the wall in your parent&#x27;s kitchen. You hop on your bike and pedal down to my end of the neighborhood.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;images&#x2F;thin_lizzy_tl.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; 
width=&quot;250&quot;&#x2F;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
            </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
